CONSTANTIN TUDOSIE

46 Winchester Ave, Yonkers, NY 10710 ● 646-327-4550 ● c tudosie@yahoo.com

CAREER BACKGROUND

Professional in an IT environment as a QA Tester. Experienced in testing software, web/mobile applications, operating systems, hardware and networks. Over 4 years of experience in the Insurance Industry with proven record of performance as an individual contributor as well as effective team player to achieve a common goal. Meticulous, attention to details and effective communicator, skills developed on the job and as a member of Toastmasters International.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Technical Specification Analysis, Test Plans & Cases, Defect & Bug Discovery
- Functional, Acceptance, Performance, Integration, Regression and Load Testing
- Tracking, Logging & Reporting, Issue Identification & Documentation
 - Bug Tracking Tools: JIRA, IssueTrak
 - Light Automation (Selenium) and SQL background
 - Web Browser: IE9/10/11, Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Safari
 - Software: Excel, Access, Word, Outlook, Visual Studio, Lotus Notes, VMware, Peachtree
- OS: Windows 10, Windows 7, Windows Vista, Windows Server 2003, Windows XP, Mac OS X Mountain Lion, Mac OS X Lion, Mac OS X Snow Leopard, Linux Fedora, Linux Ubuntu

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2014 - May 2017

Software QA / Tester

New York Life Ins

Co (through nextSource)

Sleepy Hollow, NY

- Developed and executed test plans and test cases for multiple Portal websites developed, sponsored and maintained by New York Life for its third party administrators, group insured administrators and policyholders.
 - Performed functional/performance testing on applications using manual testing.
 - Assisted in overall configuration, coordination, troubleshooting of customized applications.
- Developed and executed test plans and test cases in the upgrade process for LifeSuite software (an internal Medical Underwriting system) from 5.0 to 7.0 version, and tested it in Unit, Model and Production environments.
 - Provided online inquiry capabilities and standard reporting tools and assisted in overall LifeSuite upgrade.
- Worked closely with the vendor (StoneRiver) to assure perfect communication of the LifeSuite,
 FileNet and DataCap systems in Unit, Model and Production environments.
 - Performed functional testing on multi browsers for portal and underwriting applications.
 - Identifying errors and log reporting in JIRA and IssueTrak.
 - Participate in daily status meetings on QA testing progress.

May 2013 -Mar 2014

Service Area Consultant

New York Life Ins

Co (through nextSource)

Sleepy Hollow, NY

- Assisted with the transition of application process and paper records to digital.
- Sorted, organized and shipped company's paper records to storage facility.
- Supported underwriters and service associates in daily tasks, projects and activities as directed.
- Software: LifeSuite, Omni-Rim, Rumba, Microsoft Office, IBM Lotus, MAC, DMS

Feb 2012 - Sep 2012

IT Help Desk Intern

Cake & Arrow

 Coordinated office move and relocation of IT infrastructure: racking all the equipment, wiring the network, servers, workstations and troubleshot network equipment and set up computers, ensuring connectivity and functionality.

New York, NY

- Configured and maintained network devices, computers, printers, routers, access points.
- Diagnosed and repaired both hardware and software on Windows and Mac computers.
- Installed and upgraded Operating Systems and Software on Windows and Mac computers.

EDUCATION

York College, City University of New York - May 2010 BS in Information Systems Management Science

Minor in Computer

LANGUAGES AND INTERESTS

- Fluent in multiple languages: English, Romanian, Spanish, Italian
 Member of Legends of Sleepy Hollow Toastmasters Club